Rose Gerlach Slide Collection
Yale University Arts Library
Rose Gerlach Slide Collection
1960-1980
VRC 107
Yale University Arts Library
10.33
47 boxes
Collection consists of 8,874 slides of paintings and sculpture by various contemporary artists exhibiting in the New York area during the 1960s and 1970s, as well as gallery exhibitions of material from various sources. Artist names are accompanied by venue information.
Gerlach, Rose
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
Collection consists of 8,874 slides of paintings and sculpture by various contemporary artists exhibiting in the New York area during the 1960s and 1970s, as well as gallery exhibitions of material from various sources. Artist names are accompanied by venue information.
Arrangement
The slides are arranged alphabetically be the artists' or groups' names.
Art, Modern -- 20th Century; Art -- United States; Art, American -- 20th Century -- Exhibitions; Slides; Reproductions
- Aach, Herb, 1923-1985 [Slide box 1] (Box 1)
  - Wise Gallery, 1967 (2 slides) (Box 1)
- Abrams, Isaac, b. 1939 (Box 1)
  - East Hampton gallery, 1967, 1968 (18 slides) (Box 1)
- Acconci, Vito, b. 1940 (Box 1)
  - Sonnabend gallery, 1972 (2 slides) (Box 1)
- Adams, Alice, b. 1930 (Box 1)
  - Fischbach gallery, 1966 (1 slide) (Box 1)
- Adams, Pat, b. 1928 (Box 1)
  - Zabriskie gallery, 1972 (2 slides) (Box 1)
- Adams, Robert, 1917-1984 (Box 1)
  - Schaefer gallery, 1967 (1 slide) (Box 1)
- Adzak, Roy, b. 1927 (Box 1)
  - Sachs gallery, 1966 (7 slides) (Box 1)
- Adler, Lee, b. 1934 (Box 1)
  - Ruth White gallery, 1968 (6 slides) (Box 1)
- Adler, Myril (Box 1)
  - West Broadway gallery, 1973 (1 slide) (Box 1)
- Adler, Robert (Box 1)
  - Poindexter gallery, 1968 (5 slides) (Box 1)
- Adler, Samuel, 1898-1979 (Box 1)
  - Rehn gallery, 1971 (4 slides) (Box 1)
- Aeppli, Eva (Box 1)
  - Iolas gallery, 1970 (4 slides) (Box 1)
- African Masks (Box 1)
  - D'Hautbarrt gallery, 1967 (17 slides) (Box 1)
- Afro, 1912-1976 (Box 1)
  - Viviano gallery, 1968 (3 slides) (Box 1)
- Agam, Yaacov, b. 1928 (Box 1)
  - Denise Rene gallery, 1971 (2 slides) (Box 1)
- Agostini, Peter, 1913-1993 (Box 1)
  - Radich gallery, 1964, 1968 (7 slides) (Box 1)
- Ahn (Dong Kuk) (Box 1)
  - Green Mountain gallery, 1972 (5 slides) (Box 1)
- Ajay, Abe, b. 1919 (33 slides) (Box 1)
  - Rose Fried gallery, 1964, 1966, 1968 (Box 1)
  - Gimpel gallery, 1973 (Box 1)
- Alcalay, Albert, b. 1917 (Box 1)
  - Krasner gallery, 1966 (6 slides) (Box 1)
- Aldaraca (Box 1)
  - Amel gallery, 1965 (2 Slides) (Box 1)
- Alechinsky, Pierre, b. 1927 (Box 1)
  - Lefebre gallery, 1967, 1968, 1970, 1972, 1973 (15 slides) (Box 1)
- Alex, Kosta, b. 1925 (Box 1)
  - Lefebre gallery, 1969 (3 slides) (Box 1)
- Alexander, Peter, b. 1939 (Box 1)
  - Elkon gallery, 1969 (2 slides) (Box 1)
- Alt, Otmar, b. 1940 (Box 1)
  - Gimpel gallery, 1971 (3 slides) (Box 1)
- Altoon, John, 1925-1969 (Box 1)
  - Fischbach gallery, 1966 (2 slides) (Box 1)
- Amino, Leo, 1911-1989 (Box 1)
  - East Hampton gallery, 1969, 1970 (7 slides) (Box 1)
- Anastasi, William, b. 1933 (3 slides) (Box 1)
  - Dwan gallery, 1966 (Box 1)
  - OK Harris gallery, 1973 (Box 1)
- Andrade, Edna (12 slides) (Box 1)
  - East Hampton gallery, 1967, 1968, 1969 (Box 1)
- Andre, Carl, b. 1935 (9 slides) (Box 1)
  - Tibor de Nagy gallery, 1966 (Box 1)
  - Dwan gallery, 1969, 1971 (Box 1)
  - Weber gallery, 1972 (Box 1)
- Annesley, David, b. 1936 (6 slides) (Box 1)
  - Poindexter gallery, 1966, 1968 (Box 1)
- Antes, Horst, b. 1936 (18 slides) [Slide box 2] (Box 1)
  - Lefebre gallery, 1966, 1967, 1969, 1972 (Box 1)
- Antholz, Richard (2 slides) (Box 1)
  - Bodley gallery, 1969 (Box 1)
- Antonakos, Stephen, b. 1926 (11 slides) (Box 1)
  - Fischbach gallery, 1967, 1969, 1970, 1972 (Box 1)
  - Byron gallery, undated (Box 1)
- Antunez, Nemesio, 1918-1993 (7 slides) (Box 1)
  - Bodley gallery, 1965 (Box 1)
- Anuszkiewicz, Richard, b. 1930 (3 slides) (Box 1)
  - Contemporaries gallery, 1964 (Box 1)
  - East Hampton gallery, 1965 (Box 1)
  - Martha Jackson gallery, 1965 (Box 1)
- Appel, Karel, 1921-2006 (45 slides) (Box 1)
  - Gimpel-Weitzenhof gallery, undated (Box 1)
  - Jackson gallery, 1967, 1971 (Box 1)
- Appel, Thelma (3 slides) (Box 1)
  - Kornblee gallery, 1973 (Box 1)
- Apple, Billy, b. 1935 (3 slides) (Box 1)
  - Wise gallery, 1967 (Box 1)
- Apostolides, Zoe (14 slides) (Box 1)
  - Capricorn gallery, 1967, 1969 (Box 1)
- Arakawa Shusaku, b. 1936 (5 slides) (Box 1)
  - Dwan gallery, 1967 (Box 1)
- Arias (3 slides) (Box 1)
  - Kreisler gallery, 1969 (Box 1)
- Arman, 1928-2005 (7 slides) (Box 1)
  - L. Rubin gallery, 1970, 1971 (Box 1)
  - Gibson gallery, 1973 (Box 1)
- Arner, Robert (14 slides) (Box 1)
  - Ruth White gallery, 1965, 1968 (Box 1)
- Arnold, Anne, b. 1936 (8 slides) (Box 1)
  - Fischbach gallery, 1964, 1967, 1971 (Box 1)
- Artschwager, Richard, b. 1923 (2 slides) (Box 1)
  - Leo Castelli gallery, 1972 (Box 1)
- Asher, Elise, b. 1914 (4 slides) (Box 1)
  - Wise gallery, 1964 (Box 1)
  - Schaeffer gallery, 1973 (Box 1)
- Askinizi, Norman (1 slide) (Box 1)
  - Benedek gallery, 1973 (Box 1)
- Asoma Tadashi, b. 1923 (3 slides) (Box 1)
  - Findlay gallery, 1969 (Box 1)
- Atchley, Dana, 1941-2000 (1 slide) (Box 1)
  - HFA gallery, 1966 (Box 1)
- Athena (possibly Athena Tacha?) (11 slides) (Box 1)
  - Krasner gallery, 1966 (Box 1)
- Atirnomis (5 slides) (Box 1)
  - Spectrum gallery, 1968 (Box 1)
  - Bodley gallery, 1973 (Box 1)
- Atkins, Mildred (2 slides) (Box 1)
  - Bodley gallery, 1968 (Box 1)
- Avedesian, Edward, b. 1936 (21 slides) (Box 1)
  - Elkon gallery, 1965, 1966, 1968, 1970, 1971, 1972 (Box 1)
- Avery, Milton, 1885-1965 (12 slides) (Box 1)
  - Borgenicht gallery, 1972 (Box 1)
  - Parke-Bernet (Box 1)
  - Andre Emmerich, 1973 (Box 1)
- Aylon, Helene, b. 1931 (2 slides) [Slide box 3] (Box 1)
  - Hutchinson gallery, 1972 (Box 1)
- Ay-o, b. 1931 (7 slides) (Box 1)
  - Smolin gallery, 1964 (Box 1)
- Baber, Alice, 1928-1982 (23 slides) (Box 1)
  - Sachs gallery, 1966, 1969, 1971, 1973 (Box 1)
- Baer, Hortense (2 slides) (Box 1)
  - East Hampton, 1969 (Box 1)
- Baer, Jo, b. 1929 (4 slides) (Box 1)
  - Fischbach gallery, 1966 (Box 1)
- Baertling, Olle, 1911-1981 (8 slides) (Box 1)
  - Rose Fried gallery, 1967, 1968 (Box 1)
- Bailey, Roy (26 slides) (Box 1)
  - Hammer gallery, 1967, 1969, 1971, 1973 (Box 1)
- Bakaty, Mike, b. 1936 (3 slides) (Box 1)
  - Paley and Lowe gallery, 1971 (Box 1)
- Baker, Jack (22 slides) (Box 1)
  - Bodley gallery, 1968 (Box 1)
- Balart, Waldo Diaz, b. 1931 (4 slides) (Box 1)
  - Graham gallery, 1970, 1972 (Box 1)
- Baldesarri, John, b. 1931 (2 slides) (Box 1)
  - Feigen gallery, 1970 (Box 1)
- Balog, Michael, b. 1946 (2 slides) (Box 1)
  - Leo Castelli gallery, 1972 (Box 1)
- Bang, Thomas, b. 1938 (4 slides) (Box 1)
  - OK Harris, 1971, 1972 (Box 1)
- Bannard, Walter Darby, b. 1934 (12 slides) (Box 1)
  - Tibor de Nagy, 1966, 1967, 1968, 1969 (Box 1)
  - Rubin gallery, 1972, 1973 (Box 1)
- Barbeau, Marcel, b. 1925 (5 slides) (Box 1)
  - Farleigh-Dickinson University, 1965 (Box 1)
  - East Hampton, 1966, 1967 (Box 1)
- Barber, Allen (1 slide) (Box 1)
  - Schaefer gallery, 1965 (Box 1)
- Bardazzi, Peter, b. 1943 (5 slides) (Box 1)
  - Cordier-Ekstrom gallery, 1971, 1972 (Box 1)
- Bardone, Guy, b. 1927 (6 slides) (Box 1)
  - Findlay gallery, 1968 (Box 1)
- Barnes, Clyde (5 slides) (Box 1)
  - Phoenix gallery, 1965 (Box 1)
- Barnett, Will, b. 1911 (10 slides0 (Box 1)
  - Waddell gallery, 1965, 1968, 1970 (Box 1)
- Barr, Victoria (6 slides) (Box 1)
  - Myers gallery, 1970, 1971 (Box 1)
- Barringer (11 slides) (Box 1)
  - Schaeffer gallery, 1965 (Box 1)
  - Dwan gallery, 1967 (Box 1)
- Bart, Robert (4 slides) (Box 1)
  - Leo Castelli gallery, 1965 (Box 1)
- Bartlett, Jennifer, b. 1941 (3 slides) (Box 1)
  - Palley gallery, 1972 (Box 1)
- Baruchello, Gianfranco, b. 1924 (7 slides) (Box 1)
  - Cordier-Ekstrom, 1964, 1966 (Box 1)
- Baschet, Bernard and Francois (15 slides) (Box 1)
  - Grippi-Waddell gallery, 1965, 1970, 1971 (Box 1)
- Basën (2 slides) (Box 1)
  - Stone gallery, 1965 (Box 1)
- Baskin, Leonard, 1922-2000 (1 slide) (Box 1)
  - Byron gallery, undated (Box 1)
- Battenberg, John, b. 1931 (1 slide) (Box 1)
  - Krasner gallery, 1969 (Box 1)
- Bauermeister, Mary, b. 1934 (24 slides) [Slide box 4] (Box 1)
  - Bonino gallery, 1965, 1966, 1967, 1970 (Box 1)
  - Staempfli gallery, 1971 (Box 1)
- Baum (possibly Marilyn, b. 1939) (5 slides) (Box 1)
  - Westerly gallery, 1966 (Box 1)
- Baum, Don, b. 1922 (4 slides) (Box 1)
  - Bridge gallery, 1965 (Box 1)
- Baumbach (8 slides) (Box 1)
  - Rose Fried gallery, 1966, 1970 (Box 1)
- Bayer, Herbert, 1900-1985 (8 slides0 (Box 1)
  - Byron gallery, 1965 (Box 1)
- Beal, Jack, b. 1931 (15 slides) (Box 1)
  - Frumkin gallery, 1967, 1968, 1970, 1972 (Box 1)
- Bearden, Romare, 1911-1988 (2 slides) (Box 1)
  - Cordier-Ekstrom gallery, 1970 (Box 1)
- Beasley, Bruce, b. 1939 (2 slides) (Box 1)
  - Andre Emmerich gallery, 1971 (Box 1)
- Beauchamp, Robert, 1923-1995 (8 slides) (Box 1)
  - Graham gallery, 1966 (Box 1)
  - French gallery, 1972 (Box 1)
- Bechtle, Robert, b. 1932 (1 slide) (Box 1)
  - OK Harris, 1971 (Box 1)
- Beck, Margit (2 slides) (Box 1)
  - Babcock gallery, 1966 (Box 1)
- Beckman, William, b. 1942 (4 slides) (Box 1)
  - Allan Stone gallery, 1970 (Box 1)
- Beerman, Miriam, b. 1923 (3 slides) (Box 1)
  - Graham gallery, 1972 (Box 1)
- Bejar, Feliciano (11 slides) (Box 1)
  - Schaefer gallery, 1966, 1968, 1971 (Box 1)
- Beling, Helen (2 slides) (Box 1)
  - Krasner gallery, 1969 (Box 1)
- Bell, Larry, b. 1939 (1 slide) (Box 1)
  - Pace gallery, 1970 (Box 1)
- Benglis, Lynda, b. 1941 (8 slides) (Box 1)
  - Paula Cooper gallery, 1971, 1974, 1983, 1984 (Box 1)
- Benkert, Ernst (3 slides) (Box 1)
  - Jackson gallery, 1965 (Box 1)
- Benow, Sheila, b. 1939 (3 slides) (Box 1)
  - Molesworth gallery, 1970 (Box 1)
- Benson (6 slides) (Box 1)
  - Stable gallery, 1966 (Box 1)
- Benton, Fletcher, b. 1931 (7 slides) (Box 1)
  - Bonino gallery, 1968, 1969 (Box 1)
- Bergman (2 slides) (Box 1)
  - Spectrum gallery, 1969 (Box 1)
- Berkley, Sheila (2 slides) (Box 1)
  - Kornblee gallery, 1971 (Box 1)
- Berkon, Martin (4 slides) (Box 1)
  - 20th Century West gallery, 1967 (Box 1)
- Berkowitz, Leon, 1919-1987 (6 slides) (Box 1)
  - Sachs gallery, 1969 (Box 1)
- Bermowitz, Allen (3 slides) (Box 1)
  - OK Harris gallery, 1972, 1973 (Box 1)
- Berthold, Joachim, b. 1917 (1 slide) (Box 1)
  - Findlay gallery, 1968 1 slide (Box 1)
- Bertoia, Harry, 1915-1978 (17 slides) (Box 1)
  - Staempfli gallery, 1967, 1968, 1970, 1972 (Box 1)
- Betts, Edward, b. 1920 (6 slides) (Box 1)
  - Midtown gallery, 1968, 1971 (Box 1)
- Bhausar, Natuar (3 slides) (Box 1)
  - Max Hutchinson gallery, 1971 (Box 1)
- Bianco (5 slides) (Box 1)
  - Graham gallery, 1969 (Box 1)
- Bidner, Robert, 1930-1983 (10 slides) (Box 1)
  - Sachs gallery, 1969 (Box 1)
- Biederman, Charles, 1906-2004 (1 slide) (Box 1)
  - Zabriskie gallery, 1972 (Box 1)
- Biehl (1 slide) (Box 1)
  - Banfer gallery, 1966 (Box 1)
- Bieser, N. (1 slide) (Box 1)
  - N. Hoffman gallery, 1973 (Box 1)
- Bigelow, Chandler (3 slides) (Box 1)
  - Wickersham gallery, 1969 (Box 1)
- Bill, Max, 1908-1984 (30 slides) [Slide box 5] (Box 1)
  - Staempfli gallery, 1966, 1969, 1970 (Box 1)
- Binder, Joseph, 1898-1972 (6 slides) (Box 1)
  - Rose Fried gallery, 1969 (Box 1)
- Binford, Julien, 1908-1997 (2 slides) (Box 1)
  - Midtown gallery, 1966 2 slides (Box 1)
- Bireline, George, 1923-2002 (3 slides) (Box 1)
  - Andre Emmerich gallery, 1965 (Box 1)
- Bishop, James, b. 1927 (6 slides) (Box 1)
  - Fischbach gallery, 1968, 1970, 1972 (Box 1)
- Bissier, Julius, 1893-1965 (15 slides) (Box 1)
  - Lefebre gallery, 1966 (Box 1)
- Bladen, Ron, 1918-1988 (2 slides) (Box 1)
  - Fischbach gallery, 1971, 1972 (Box 1)
- Blagdon, Allen, b. 1938 (15 slides) (Box 1)
  - Milch gallery, 1966 (Box 1)
  - F. Rehn gallery, 1968 (Box 1)
  - Ruth White gallery, 1968 (Box 1)
- Blaine, Nell, 1922-1996 (9 slides) (Box 1)
  - Bodley gallery, 1969 (Box 1)
  - Fischbach gallery, 1978, 1981, 1983 (Box 1)
- Blayton, Betty, b. 1937 (5 slides) (Box 1)
  - Capricorn gallery, 1967 (Box 1)
- Blitt, Rita (2 slides) (Box 1)
  - Spectrum gallery, 1969 (Box 1)
- Boardman, Seymour (8 slides) (Box 1)
  - Sachs gallery, 1967, 1968, 1969 (Box 1)
- Bochner, Mel, b. 1940 (7 slides) (Box 1)
  - Sonnabend gallery, 1967, 1972, 1973 (Box 1)
- Boetti, Alighiero (4 slides) (Box 1)
  - Weber gallery, 1973, 1975 (Box 1)
- Bogart, Richard (31 slides) (Box 1)
  - Poindexter gallery, 1967, 1968, 1970 (Box 1)
- Boghosian, Varujan, b. 1926 (26 slides) (Box 1)
  - Stable gallery, 1966, 1964 (Box 1)
  - Cordier-Ekstrom, 1969, 1971 (Box 1)
- Boix-Vives, Anselmo, b. 1899 (5 slides) (Box 1)
  - Lefebre gallery, 1966 (Box 1)
- Bollinger, Bill (3 slides) (Box 1)
  - O.K. Harris gallery, 1972, 1973 (Box 1)
- Bolotowsky, Ilya, 1907-1981 (33 slides) [Slide box 6] (Box 1)
  - Borgenicht gallery, 1965, 1966, 1968, 1970, 1972 (Box 1)
- Boltanski, Christian, b. 1944 (1 slide) (Box 1)
  - Sonnabend gallery, 1973 (Box 1)
- Bolws (5 slides) (Box 1)
  - Kornblee gallery, 1966 (Box 1)
- Bond, Douglas, b. 1937 (1 slide) (Box 1)
  - O.K. Harris gallery, 1973 (Box 1)
- Bonevardi, Marcelo, 1929-1994 (7 slides) (Box 1)
  - Bonino gallery, 1965, 1967 (Box 1)
- Bonham, Don (2 slides) (Box 1)
  - Benedek gallery, 1973 (Box 1)
- Bontecou, Lee, b. 1931 (7 slides) (Box 1)
  - Castelli gallery, 1966 (Box 1)
- Boothe, Power, b. 1945 (2 slides) (Box 1)
  - Sachs gallery, 1973, 1974 (Box 1)
- Borduas, (Paul?) (1 slide) (Box 1)
  - Martha Jackson gallery, 1964 (Box 1)
- Borgatta (4 slides) (Box 1)
  - Babcock gallery, 1969 (Box 1)
- Bosson, Jack, b. 1937 (2 slides) (Box 1)
  - Fischback gallery, 1972 (Box 1)
- Boterf, Check (17 slides) (Box 1)
  - Tibor de Nagy gallery, 1967, 1968 (Box 1)
  - Myers gallery, 1971 (Box 1)
- Botero, Fernando (1 slide) (Box 1)
  - Bonino gallery, 1964 (Box 1)
- Botkin, Henry, 1896-1983 (8 slides) (Box 1)
  - Rehn gallery, 1966, 1970 (Box 1)
- Bower, Gary, b. 1940 (3 slides) (Box 1)
  - O.K. Harris gallery, 1972 (Box 1)
- Bowman, Ken (4 slides) (Box 1)
  - Tibor de Nagy gallery, 1970, 1973 (Box 1)
- Box Show (Various Artists) (8 slides) (Box 1)
  - Byron gallery, 2/13/1965 (Box 1)
- Boxer, Stanley, b. 1926 (12 slides) (Box 1)
  - Rose Fried gallery, 1968 (Box 1)
  - Tibor de Nagy gallery, 1971, 1972, 1973 (Box 1)
- Brach, Paul, b. 1924 (1 slide) (Box 1)
  - Kornblee gallery, 1968 (Box 1)
- Bradley, Peter, b. 1940 (6 slides) (Box 1)
  - Emmerich gallery, 1972, 1973 (Box 1)
- Brady, Carolyn (8 slides) (Box 1)
  - Nancy Hoffman gallery, 1977, 1981, 1982, 1983, 1984 (Box 1)
- Braquin, Simeon (3 slides) (Box 1)
  - Poindexter gallery, 1971 (Box 1)
- Brainerd, Joe (19 slides) (Box 1)
  - Alan gallery, 1965 (Box 1)
  - Fischbach, 1971, 1972 (Box 1)
- Brandt, Sharon (2 slides) (Box 1)
  - O.K. Harris gallery, 1972 (Box 1)
- Brandt, Warren, 1918-2002 (10 slides) (Box 1)
  - Sachs gallery, 1970, 1972, 1973 (Box 1)
- Brauner, Victor, 1903-1966 (17 slides) (Box 1)
  - Iolas gallery, 1966, 1971 (Box 1)
- Bravo (2 slides) [Slide box 7] (Box 2)
  - Staempfli gallery, 1971 (Box 2)
- Breder, Hans, b. 1935(7 slides) (Box 2)
  - Feigen gallery, 1967, 1970 (Box 2)
  - Hutchinson gallery, 1973 (Box 2)
- Breer, Robert, b. 1926 (2 slides) (Box 2)
  - Bonino gallery, 1965 (Box 2)
- Brendel, Bettina (9 slides) (Box 2)
  - Spectrum gallery, 1967 (Box 2)
- Brenner (4 slides) (Box 2)
  - Grand Central Moderns, 1967 (Box 2)
- Brizzi, Ary, b. 1930 (1 slide) (Box 2)
  - Bonino gallery, 1968 (Box 2)
- Brody, Joel (4 slides) (Box 2)
  - Tibor de Nagy gallery, 1966 (Box 2)
- Brooks, James, 1906-1992 (15 slides) (Box 2)
  - Jackson gallery, 1968, 1971, 1972 (Box 2)
- Brosse, Mark (2 slides) (Box 2)
  - Sachs gallery, 1966 (Box 2)
- Browler, Miriam (1 slide) (Box 2)
  - Sachs gallery, 1969 (Box 2)
- Brown, Alice Dalton (4 slides) (Box 2)
  - Sachs gallery, 1981, 1982, 1983 (Box 2)
- Brown, David Lee, b. 1939 (2 slides) (Box 2)
  - Borgenicht gallery, 1970 (Box 2)
- Brown, Gordon (3 slides) (Box 2)
  - Ruth White gallery, 1968 (Box 2)
- Brown, Joan (5 slides) (Box 2)
  - Frumkin gallery, 1982, 1983 (Box 2)
- Brown, Judith (2 slides) (Box 2)
  - Byron gallery, 1966 (Box 2)
- Brusca, Jack, 1939-1993 (7 slides) (Box 2)
  - Bonino gallery, 1970, 1973 (Box 2)
- Buchenholtz (9 slides) (Box 2)
  - Ruth White gallery, 1965 (Box 2)
- Buchwald, Howard, b. 1943 (1 slide) (Box 2)
  - N. Hoffman gallery, 1973 (Box 2)
- Bücker (6 slides) (Box 2)
  - Feigen gallery, 1966 (Box 2)
- Bulman, Orville (2 slides) (Box 2)
  - Hammer gallery, 1967 (Box 2)
- Bunuel, Luis, 1900-1983 (5 slides) (Box 2)
  - Willard gallery, 1965 (Box 2)
- Burchfield (8 slides) (Box 2)
  - Rehn gallery, 1966 (Box 2)
- Buren, Daniel, b. 1938 (2 slides) (Box 2)
  - Weber gallery, 1973 (Box 2)
- Burke, Ainslie (12 slides) (Box 2)
  - Kraushaar gallery, 1967 (Box 2)
- Burlin, Paul, 1886-1969 (1 slide) (Box 2)
  - Borgenicht gallery, 1971 (Box 2)
- Bury, Pol, b. 1922 (29 slides) (Box 2)
  - Lefebre gallery, 1964, 1966, 1968, 1971 (Box 2)
- Bush, Jack, 1909-1977 (12 slides) (Box 2)
  - Emmerich gallery, 1967, 1970, 1972 (Box 2)
- Butchkes (2 slides) (Box 2)
  - Amel gallery, 1965 (Box 2)
- Butor (5 slides) (Box 2)
  - Grippi-Waddell gallery, 1965 (Box 2)
- Button, John, b. 1929 (15 slides) (Box 2)
  - Kornblee gallery, 1968, 1970, 1972 (Box 2)
  - Grippi-Waddell gallery, 1973 (Box 2)
- Calabro, Richard, b. 1937 (2 slides) [Slide box 8] (Box 2)
  - Hutchinson gallery, 1972 (Box 2)
- Calcagno, Lawrence, 1913-1993 (5 slides) (Box 2)
  - Osborne gallery, 1964 (Box 2)
- Calder, Alexander, 1898-1976 (5 slides) (Box 2)
  - Krasner gallery, 1967 (Box 2)
  - Guggenheim gallery, 1964 (Box 2)
  - Lincoln Center plaza, 1973 (Box 2)
- Calzolari, Pier Paolo, b. 1943 (6 slides) (Box 2)
  - Sonnabend gallery, 1971 (Box 2)
- Camargo (13 slides) (Box 2)
  - Gimpel gallery, 1969 (Box 2)
- Campbell (1 slide) (Box 2)
  - Grand Central Moderns, 1966 (Box 2)
- Campbell, Gretna, 1922-1987 (3 slides) (Box 2)
  - Green Mt. gallery, 1973 (Box 2)
- Candelaire (5 slides) (Box 2)
  - Jackson gallery, 1965 (Box 2)
- Canin, Martin, b. 1927 (7 slides) (Box 2)
  - Graham gallery, 1968, 1969 (Box 2)
- Canogar, Rafael Gomez, b. 1935 (5 slides) (Box 2)
  - Schaefer gallery, 1967 (Box 2)
- Canright (4 slides) (Box 2)
  - Pam Adler gallery, 1982, 1983 (Box 2)
- Cappelletto (4 slides) (Box 2)
  - Pam Adler gallery, 1983 (Box 2)
- Capraris, Milley (6 slides) (Box 2)
  - East Hampton gallery, 1968 (Box 2)
- Cardenas (1 slide) (Box 2)
  - Kreisler gallery, 1969 (Box 2)
- Carey (2 slides) (Box 2)
  - Cordier-Ekstrom gallery, 1969 (Box 2)
- Carlo (2 slides) (Box 2)
  - Cordier-Ekstrom gallery, 1972 (Box 2)
- Caro, Anthony, b. 1924 (6 slides) (Box 2)
  - Emmerich, 1966, 1968, 1972 (Box 2)
- Carr, David (2 slides) (Box 2)
  - Schaeffer gallery, 1969 (Box 2)
- Carrel, Claudia (11 slides) (Box 2)
  - East Hampton gallery, 1967, 1968, 1970 (Box 2)
- Carsman, Jon, 1944-1987 (3 slides) (Box 2)
  - Graham gallery, 1969, 1971 (Box 2)
- Carter, Clarence, 1904-2000 (13 slides) (Box 2)
  - Rose Fried gallery, 1966 (Box 2)
- Castagna, Pino (1 slide) (Box 2)
  - Bonino gallery, 1964 (Box 2)
- Castanis, Muriel, 1926-2006 (5 slides) (Box 2)
  - Ruth White gallery, 1968 (Box 2)
- Castel (16 slides) (Box 2)
  - Lefebre gallery, 1966, 1969 (Box 2)
- Castelli Warehouse (Exhibition) 1968 (7 slides) (Box 2)
  - Artists: (Box 2)
    - Anselmo (Box 2)
    - Bollinger, Bill (Box 2)
    - Hesse, Eva (Box 2)
    - Saret, Alan (Box 2)
    - Serra, Richard (Box 2)
    - Sonnier, Keith (Box 2)
    - Zorio, Gilberto (Box 2)
- Castillo (2 slides) (Box 2)
  - Bodley gallery, 1965 (Box 2)
- Castori (1 slide) (Box 2)
  - Tibor de Nagy gallery, 1966 (Box 2)
- Castro-Cid, Enrique, b. 1937 (10 slides) (Box 2)
  - Feigen gallery, 1965, 1966, 1968 (Box 2)
- Cathelin, Bernard, 1919-2004 (18 slides) (Box 2)
  - Findlay gallery, 1966, 1968, 1973 (Box 2)
- Caulfield, Patrick, b. 1936 (3 slides) (Box 2)
  - Elkon gallery, 1968 (Box 2)
- Cavallon, Giorgio, 1904-1989 (9 slides) [Slide box 9] (Box 2)
  - Sachs gallery, 1969, 1971 (Box 2)
- Ceen (8 slides) (Box 2)
  - Bodley gallery, 1965 (Box 2)
- Celender, Donald, 1932-2005 (1 slide) (Box 2)
  - O.K. Harris, 1971 (Box 2)
- Celentino (20 slides) (Box 2)
  - Wise gallery, 1964, 1966 (Box 2)
  - FDU, 1965 (Box 2)
- Celis (1 slide) (Box 2)
  - Kreisler gallery, 1970 (Box 2)
- Celmins, Vija (4 slides) (Box 2)
  - KcKee gallery, 1977, 1983 (Box 2)
- Ceroli, Mario, b. 1938 (7 slides) (Box 2)
  - Bonino gallery, 1967 (Box 2)
- Chaet, Bernard, b. 1924 (11 slides) (Box 2)
  - Stable gallery, 1967 (Box 2)
- Chaissal (2 slides) (Box 2)
  - Cordier-Ekstrom gallery, 1966 (Box 2)
- Chalem, Celine (5 slides) (Box 2)
  - M. Jackson gallery, 1967 (Box 2)
- Chamberlain, John, b. 1927 (8 slides) (Box 2)
  - Castelli, 1964, 1968, 1971, 1973 (Box 2)
- Chandra, (Avinash?) (1 slide) (Box 2)
  - Rose Fried gallery, 1968 (Box 2)
- Chang, Dai-Chien (2 slides) (Box 2)
  - Caro gallery, 1968 (Box 2)
- Chapin (3 slides) (Box 2)
  - O.K. Harris gallery, 1971 (Box 2)
- Chase, Doris Totten, b. 1923 (16 slides) (Box 2)
  - Ruth White gallery, 1969, 1967 (Box 2)
  - Emmerich gallery, 1969 (Box 2)
- Chinn, Yuen-Yuey (5 slides) (Box 2)
  - Byron gallery, 1966 (Box 2)
- Chermayeff, Ivan. B. 1932 (3 slides) (Box 2)
  - Gimpel gallery, 1971 (Box 2)
- Chihuly, Dale. B. 1941 (2 slides) (Box 2)
  - Museum of Contemporary Crafts, Glass, 1971 (Box 2)
- Childs, Bernard, 1910-1985 (2 slides) (Box 2)
  - Schaeffer gallery, 1973 (Box 2)
- Chirino, Martin, b. 1925 (2 slides) (Box 2)
  - Borgenicht gallery, 1969 (Box 2)
- Christo, b. 1935 (4 slides) (Box 2)
  - Castelli, 1966, 1967 (Box 2)
- Chung, Kim (4 slides) (Box 2)
  - Krasner gallery, 1969 (Box 2)
- Christ-Janer, Albert, 1910-1973 (4 slides) (Box 2)
  - Krasner gallery, 1968 (Box 2)
- Christensen, Dan, 1942-2007 (8 slides) (Box 2)
  - Emmerich gallery, 1969, 1971 (Box 2)
- Chryssa, Varda, b. 1933 (7 slides) (Box 2)
  - Pace gallery, 1968 (Box 2)
  - Denise René gallery, 1973 (Box 2)
- Church, Dee (2 slides) (Box 2)
  - Bridge gallery, 1964 (Box 2)
- Ciarrochi, Ray (5 slides) (Box 2)
  - Tibor de Nagy gallery, 1971, 1972, 1974 (Box 2)
- Cibula, Ellen (2 slides) (Box 2)
  - O.K. Harris gallery, 1970 (Box 2)
- Cicero, Carmen (8 slides) (Box 2)
  - Peridot gallery, 1968 (Box 2)
- Citron, Minna Wright, 1896-1991 (14 slides) (Box 2)
  - Jason gallery, 1966 (Box 2)
  - Tasca gallery, 1964 (Box 2)
- Civitello (1 slide) [Slide box 10] (Box 2)
  - Sachs gallery, 1972 (Box 2)
- Clague, John Rogers, b. 1928 (13 slides) (Box 2)
  - Grippi-Waddell gallery, 1965, 1966 (Box 2)
- Claisse, Genevieve, b. 1935 (5 slides) (Box 2)
  - Denise Renee gallery, 1974 (Box 2)
- Clark, Edward, b. 1926 (1 slide) (Box 2)
  - Prince St. gallery, 1972 (Box 2)
- Clarke, John Clem, b. 1937 (10 slides) (Box 2)
  - Kornblee gallery, 1968, 1969, 1970 (Box 2)
  - O.K. Harris gallery, 1972, 1975 (Box 2)
- Clemente (5 slides) (Box 2)
  - Castelli gallery (Box 2)
- Close, Chuck, b. 1940 (5 slides) (Box 2)
  - Bykert gallery, 1970, 1971 (Box 2)
- Clutz, William "Bill," b. 1933 (9 slides) (Box 2)
  - Schaefer gallery, 1967, 1969 (Box 2)
  - Graham gallery, 1972 (Box 2)
- Cohen, George, b. 1919 (12 slides) (Box 2)
  - Feigen gallery, 1964, 1966 (Box 2)
- Coiner, Charles Toucey, 1898-1989 (5 slides) (Box 2)
  - Midtown gallery, 1967, 1971 (Box 2)
- Cole, Donald, b. 1930 (1 slide) (Box 2)
  - Hoffman gallery, 1973 (Box 2)
- Colker, Edward, b. 1927 (6 slides) (Box 2)
  - East Hampton gallery, 1969 (Box 2)
- Collie, Albert (1 slide) (Box 2)
  - Nordness(?) gallery, 1964 (Box 2)
- Colmer, Roy (1 slide) (Box 2)
  - West Broadway gallery, 1973 (Box 2)
- Comins (6 slides) (Box 2)
  - Roko gallery, 1965 (Box 2)
- Concrete Poetry Visual Arts Gallery (Exhibition) 1968 (6 slides) (Box 2)
- Conde, Miguel (1 slide) (Box 2)